他没有出席与国王的会议
He didn't show up at the meeting with His Highness,
今天早上发现了他的尸体
and his body was found this morning.
法国人迫使你们的国王承认苏联主权
The French pressured your king to recognize the Soviet Union,
纳粹不喜欢这样
and the Nazis don't like that.
为什么穆斯塔法要杀了诺维奇？
And why did Mustapha kill Nowicki?
因为诺维奇可能是个纳粹间谍
Because Nowicki was probably a Nazi spy.
除了国王
Apart from the King, he was supposed to meet
- 他还要和我们组织的什么人见面 - 谁？
with someone from our organization. With whom?
如果你认为我们没有证据证明你是德国间谍
If you think we have no evidence that you are a German spy,
那你就大错特错了
you are seriously mistaken.
但如果你跟我对着干
But if you go after me,
这可能是下一期新时代报的头版
this could be, for example, the next cover of the New Age.
告诉我，这个人是谁？
Tell me, who's this man?
拉贾奇基开始调查法国人的事了
Rajachki sniffs around the Frenchman.
穆斯塔法，做点什么吧，他会发现我的
Mustapha, do something, he will find me.
你想再买一个铅矿？
You would like us to buy a lead mine? Again?
到目前为止，他一分钱也没付
He hasn't paid anything so far.
停止合作，直到另行通知
Stop it until further notice.
马其顿有点麻烦，阿尔索夫回来了
We have a situation in Macedonia. Hadzi Arsov is back.
我们在哪里给你鸦片？
Where can we deliver opium to you?
不是鸦片，是海洛因
Not opium. Heroin.
我要你把我介绍给你的老板
I want you to introduce me to your boss.
修道士会记住这一点
The Monk will remember this.
贝尔格莱德的纽约！
New York in Belgrade!
托马斯维奇是科罗沙克的人
Tomasovich is Koroshac's man.
除掉他
Get rid of him.
继续调查法官，找出他的所有资料
Get back to the judge. Find everything about him.
从一战到现在，特别是一战
From the World War I until now. Especially the World War I.
法官是建设新纪念碑
The judge was on the Committee
委员会的成员
for the construction of the new monument.
他嗜赌如命
He's known as a passionate gambler.
地下赌局是由迪米特里耶维奇组织的
Those poker games were organized by Dimitriyevich.
他们真的要拆除这里吗？
Are they really demolishing this?
你们所有人都应该签字，否则，亚塔汗贫民窟就不存在了
All of you should sign. Otherwise, there's no Yataghan slum.
他让你卷入了什么? 什么肮脏的勾当？
What did he get you into? What kind of dirty business?
迪米特里耶维奇听到牧师想告诉你名字
Dimitriyevich heard that the priest wanted to tell you his name.
我要离开维多杰，你应该知道要怎么做
I'm leaving Vidoje. And you see what you'll do.
如果我们之间还有什么的话
If there is still something between us.
索尼娅
SONYA
索尼娅 · 斯坦尼萨维尔耶维奇 维多杰 · 斯坦尼萨维尔耶维奇
SONYA STANISAVLJEVICH VIDOJE STANISAVLJEVICH
从现在开始，算我一个
From now on, count on me.
巴尔干半岛的阴影 第二季 第五集
BLACK SUN SEASON 2 EPISODE 05
南斯拉夫王国 达尔马提亚
HVAR, DALMATIA KINGDOM OF YUGOSLAVIA
科斯马奇少校来了
Major Kosmach is here.
科罗萨克先生
Well, Mr. Koroshac,
我不得不承认在贝尔格莱德发生了这么多事情之后
I have to admit that after all these events in Belgrade,
你的这个监狱看起来很不错
this prison of yours seems very pleasant.
科斯马奇
Kosmach.
即使栏杆是用金子做的
Prison is a prison,
监狱就是监狱
even when the bars are made of gold.
请坐
Have a seat, please.
无论如何，这里都比警局的监狱更好
It is more pleasant than Glavnjacha, in any case.
如果他们找日瓦科维奇将军商量一下
If they had asked General Zhivkovich for an opinion,
你现在可能就是在警局监狱拜访我了
you would probably have visited me in Glavnjacha now.
他们想让你知道，你对他们来说仍然很重要
They want to show you that you're still important to them.
如果你和我一样长时间从政
When you are in politics as long as I have been,
你就会学到
you learn to value only deeds,
注重行为而不是意图
not intentions.
有一件事是肯定的，因为他们同意克罗地亚人的观点
One thing is for sure, as they agreed with the Croats,
贝尔格莱德将来必须与斯洛文尼亚达成协议
Belgrade will have to make agreements with the Slovenes in the future.
贝尔格莱德的局势正在迅速变化
The situation in Belgrade is rapidly becoming more complicated,
尤其是对日瓦科维奇将军
especially for General Zhivkovich.
是的，我在报纸上看到了
Yes, I read about it.
法国外交官遇难...
The murder of the French diplomat...
真是一团糟
It's a real mess.
特别是在这样一个敏感的政治时刻
Especially at such a sensitive political moment.
相信我，很多人都想利用这件事
Many will want to take advantage of this affair, trust me.
记住加夫里洛 · 普林西普说的话
Remember Gavrilo Princip,
“在正确的时间开一枪，整个世界都会起火”
"One bullet at the right time and the world is on fire."
谢谢你
Thank you.
我没有好消息
I have no good news.
我们的计划进展不顺利
Our plan isn't going well.
托马斯维奇未能与米里奇达成协议
Tomasovich failed to reach an agreement with Mirich.
- 说得委婉点 - 情况不妙
- To put it mildly. - That's not good.
只要贝尔格莱德
As long as Belgrade
还控制着鸦片交易
has the power over the opiate trade,
我们的利益就不会被认真对待
our interests won't be taken seriously.
在我看来，我们已经没有什么好办法了
It seems to me that we no longer have a single card up in our sleeve.
是的，今天博拉岛风很大
Yes. It's windy today. Bora.
这可比南斯拉夫的风好多了
It's better than wind yugo.
南斯拉夫的风能把人吹疯
Yugo drives you crazy.
科斯马奇，你得去见托马斯维奇
Kosmach, you have to meet with Tomasovich.
找他的船来运输货物
Find him ships to transport his goods.
斯普利特港口很不错，看守不严
The port of Split is a good solution, there is weaker control.
好吧，然后呢？
Okay. And then what?
没事了
Nothing.
警告一下我们的人民
Alarm our people a bit.
让斯洛文尼亚人的声音被听到
Let the voice of the Slovenes be heard.
然后我们等待事态发展
And then we'll wait for everything to develop.
我们要等到什么时候？
We'll wait? Until when?
直到世界起火
Until the world is on fire.
别这样，我们是一条船上的
Please, don't! We're on the same side.
- 要搭车吗? - 不用了，谢谢
- Need a ride? - No, thanks.
我习惯走路了
I'm used to walking.
尽管如此，我还是希望你上车坐坐
Still, I wish you would do it for me.
- 丹尼洛 · 托马斯维奇 - 很高兴见到你
- Danilo Tomasovich. - Nice to meet you.
首先，我要感谢你
First of all, I would like to thank you.
如果不是因为你，我们就不会有这次谈话
If it weren't for you, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
举手之劳，何足挂齿
You're welcome.
我知道你是个谦虚的人，也知道你是个出色的警察
I know you're a modest man and that you were a great cop.
我不确定每个人都会同意这一点
I'm not sure everyone would agree with that.
你同意吗？
Would you agree with that?
先生，我知道
Sir, I've learned that
当你放下过去
the past stops bothering you
就不再会困扰你了
when you leave it behind.
我不这么认为
I wouldn't agree.
我的过去不想让我放下，即使是在世界的另一边
My past didn't want to leave me even on the other side of the world.
而且当下对我也不友好
And the present doesn't caress me either.
我就直说了
But let's not waste time.
我想让你为我工作
I'd like you to work for me.
我? ！
Me?!
我只是个酿酒的
I'm just an ordinary brandy producer.
像我这样的人能为你做什么？
What could a man like me do for you?
不是那样的
It's not like that.
你对这座城市了如指掌
You know this city like the back of your hand.
每条街道，每条巷子，他们都认识你
Every street, every alley, they know you in the Gun Slum.
你在亚塔汗贫民窟很受欢迎
You're appreciated in Yataghan slum.
还在警方有些关系
Your connections in the police are still fresh, so to speak.
你就是我需要的人
You are the man I need.
你错了
You're wrong.
我肯定不是你需要的人
I'm certainly not the man you need.
对不起，我们已经到站了
Excuse me! We've arrived at the station.
如果你改变主意，我的大门永远为你敞开
If you ever change your mind, my door is always open for you.
你救了我的命
You saved my life,
我不会忘记的
and I won't forget that.
托马斯维奇先生，我不了解你
Mr. Tomasovich, I don't know you.
我救你的命是个意外
I saved your life by accident.
如果我了解你
If I knew you,
我不确定我会这么做
I'm not sure I'd have done it.
所以你不欠我什么
So, you don't owe me anything.
谢谢你载我一程
Thanks for the ride.
你找到亚塔汗贫民窟的线索了吗？
Did you find out anything about Yataghan slum?
是的
I did.
怎么说？
And?
哦，每年这个时候我都很讨厌贝尔格莱德
Oh, I hate Belgrade at this time of year.
我真的很想去别的地方...开始新的生活
I'd really like to go somewhere... To a new life.
你不能逃避生活
You can't run away from life.
你可以，如果你有人可以一起私奔的话
You can. If you have someone to run away with.
你离开家乡的时候多大？
How old were you when you left your hometown?
很大了
Too old.
我明白了
I see.
不，你不明白
No, you can't understand that.
你现在还不明白
And you don't understand it now.
斯坦科，别管这事
Stanko, please stay out of this.
这是一个非常危险的游戏
This is a very dangerous game.
我很清楚我要做什么
I know exactly what I'm going to do.
你打算怎么做? 逮捕他? ！
What are you going to do? Arrest him?!
别傻了
Don't be a fool.
好吧，你到底告不告诉我？
Okay, will you tell me or not?
修道士，拉贾奇基
The Monk, Rajachki,
被谋杀的法官还有维多杰
the murdered judge and Vidoje worked on the construction
计划在亚塔汗贫民窟建造一个新的城镇
of a new town on the site of Yataghan slum
他们把国家拿来建造日尔诺夫纪念碑的大理石掉了包
and they traded the state marble needed for the monument on Zhrnov,
然后卖掉大理石，偷走了钱，骗了所有人
so they sold that marble, stole money, scamming everyone...
这是一个非常非常危险的游戏
It's a very, very dangerous game.
还有一个参与这些事情的人...
The one who's also involved in all of this is...
他们称之为塞尔维亚的戈培尔
the one they call Serbian Goebbels...
- 奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇？ - 是的，就是他
- Obrad Savkovich? - Yes, that one.
就是这样
That's it.
这些人很快就会栽在我们手里
All of them will fall into our hands very soon.
斯坦科，别自欺欺人了
Stanko, please don't fool yourself.
自从维多杰被杀后，修道士就彻底疯了
Since Vidoje was killed, the Monk's gone completely crazy.
我见过各种各样的疯子，但从没见过这样的
I've met various maniacs, but I've never met one like this.
你要弄清楚所有的情况
You have to find out all about that business.
尤其是修道士和奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇之间的联系
Especially the connection between the Monk and Obrad Savkovich.
如果我失去了你，我该怎么办？
What will I do if I lose you?
求你了! 请温柔点
Please! Be gentle, please.
什么事？
Yes?
维瑞加，进来
Veriga, come in, please.
想喝点酒吗？
Want some wine?
不用了，谢谢
No, thanks.
从世界诞生开始，在所有文明中
Wine has been a symbol of blood in all civilizations
酒都是血的象征，你知道吗？
since the world began. Did you know that?
最近在我们城市的街道上
These days blood is being poured unfairly
到处都是鲜血
on the streets of our city.
我们对此是什么立场？
Where do we stand on that?
我们杀了他的兄弟维利科
We killed his brother Velyko.
丹尼洛活了下来
Danilo survived.
他还活着？
He survived?!
那个前警察...
Well, that former cop...
你认识他，塔纳西耶维奇
You know him. Tanasiyevich.
你是说托马斯维奇还活着吗！
Are you telling me that Tomasovich is alive?!
他逃跑了
He ran away with his tail between his legs.
他不会成为我们的麻烦，相信我
He won't be a problem for us, trust me.
我怎么能相信你，白痴? ！
How can I trust you, idiot?!
你知道他们是什么人吗！
Do you even know who those people are?!
对于黑山人来说，将会有一场血腥的复仇
When it comes to Montenegrins, there is blood revenge.
我该杀了你吗？
Should I kill you, huh?
然后说你是自己干的
And say you worked on your own.
不，他们会知道我是幕后黑手，这可不妙
No, they'll know I'm behind it, and that's not good.
也许我应该接受海洛因的提议
Maybe I should have accepted the heroin job.
这是个有利可图的事情
It's a lucrative thing.
他们有很多关系
They have a lot of connections.
这是个天大的错误！
This is a big mistake. Very big mistake!
加强俱乐部的安全措施
Increase security at the club.
加强我的个人安保
Double my personal security.
我要随时知道谁在我的俱乐部里走动
I want to know at any moment who is walking around my club.
我不想在那儿树敌
I don't want enemies there.
是哪些敌人？
Which enemies exactly?
所有人！
All of them!
给你...还是热的
Here... it's still warm.
如栅，你真的不应该...又来了
Ruzha, you really shouldn't have... Again.
如栅，你要我吃醋吗？
Ruzha, you want me to get jealous?
不，警官，只是...
No, inspector, it's just...
- 那孩子... - 怎么了？
- The kid is... - What kid?
这孩子在禁食
This kid is fasting,
所以我很担心他只喝汤，并且日以继夜地工作
so I worry about how he can stand on his feet at all,
还能不能站起来
eating only soups and working day and night.
谢谢你，如栅
Thank you, Ruzha.
- 你真的在禁食吗? - 是的
- Are you really fasting? - Yes, yes.
净化身体和精神
It purifies the body and spirit.
有助于我专注于重要的事情
It helps me focus on the important things.
不用起来，坐下
No, sit down.
你是对的，但是要小心，这是件严肃的事情
You were right, but be careful. This is a serious matter.
- 我们已经联系上了... - 普莱蒂科西奇！
- We've already connected... - Pletikosich!
- 法官和维多杰...-普莱蒂科西奇，我在说话！
- The judge hung out with Vidoje... - Pletikosich, I'm talking!
对不起
Sorry.
这是一件严肃的事情，应该小心谨慎地进行
This is a serious matter and should be conducted carefully and discreetly.
如果你已经把这些人联系起来了
If you're already connecting all of these people,
要小心每一步
watch out for every step.
我不理解
I don't understand.
没什么好理解的
There's nothing to understand,
你还是像以前一样在进行调查
you're conducting an investigation as before,
但是有任何新发现你都要向我汇报
but every progress you'll report to me...
- 而且只向我汇报，明白吗? - 明白
- And only to me. Clear? - Yes.
- 萨夫科维奇先生 - 帕帕哈吉先生
- Mr. Savkovich. - Mr. Papahagi.
你不去一起开会吗？
You won't be in a meeting?
不好意思，我还有点事，不去了
Unfortunately no. I have some business in town.
但是玛雅夫人在等你
But Mrs. Maya is waiting for you.
那我先过去了
Then I'll hurry.
我在维也纳的时候你能管理这个组织
You know how grateful I am to you
我很感激你
for running the organization while I was in Vienna.
这是我的职责
That was my duty.
你做得很好
And you did it very well.
我所希望的是
What I had hoped for was that
我们最终能够对付这个腐败的政权
we'd finally get to grips with this corrupt regime.
首先是和日夫科维奇还有他那些恶心的随从
First of all, with Zhivkovich and his disgusting retinue.
我们正在努力
We're working on it.
你真该看看我给他看照片时他的表情
You should've seen his face when I showed him the photos.
很遗憾我没看到
I'm sorry I haven't.
无论如何，我希望我们能尽快让他下台
Anyway, I hope we'll see his end soon.
还有那个白痴米里奇
And the end of that idiot Mirich.
别急，很接近了
Take it easy. It's getting closer.
萨夫科维奇先生
You see, Mr. Savkovich...
我有种感觉
I have the impression
最近发生了一些奇怪的事
that some strange things have been happening lately.
我最近有一次...
I recently had one...
非常有趣的邂逅
Very interesting encounter.
你听说过穆斯塔法·戈卢比奇吗？
Have you heard of Mustapha Golubich?
是的，他在贝尔格莱德？
Yes. He's in Belgrade?
他在贝尔格莱德待了一段时间
He's been in Belgrade for some time.
共产国际突然对我们的组织产生了兴趣
The Comintern suddenly began to take an interest in our organization.
这可是新鲜事，你知道为什么吗？
That's something new. Do you know why?
因为暗杀国王的计划已经开始了
Because the assassination of the king is being planned.
谁在策划这件事？
Who's been planning it?
你说呢！
You name it!
有趣的是...
The interesting part is...
如果幕斯塔法值得信任，而且说的是事实
If Mustapha is to be believed and if that's true,
他的踪迹指向了我们的组织
his traces lead to our organization.
这是个圈套
It's a set-up.
也许吧
Maybe.
你可能是对的，但是...
You may be right, but...
我觉得最近
I have the impression that, lately,
我们组织里发生了一些
some things have been happening in our organization
我不知道的事情
without my knowledge.
- 我就直接问你了 - 什么？
- I'll ask you openly. - Yes?
在我们所有的成员中
Of all our brothers,
你是唯一有许可
you're the only one who had the permission
联系维也纳总部的人
to contact the headquarters in Vienna.
也许你知道一些我不知道的事？
Or maybe you know something I don't?
你是说诺维奇伯爵的事吗？
You mean the affair with Count Nowicki?
我从未越权
It's pointless for me to assure you
但我向你保证没有意义
that I've never exceeded my authority.
亲爱的玛雅，让我提醒你
Dear Maya, let me remind you
我们的一位杰出成员
that one of our prominent members
和维也纳的关系比你我要好得多
has much stronger connections with Vienna than you and me.
不仅因为他的工作性质
Both because of the nature of his job
还因为他的背景
and because of his background.
拉贾奇基
Rajachki.
大爷，来玩啊！
Wow, gentlemen! Come here! Come on!
米伦，你怎么来了？
Milun, how come you're here?
萨夫卡，快离开这里！
Savka, get outta here!
- 服务员! - 老板！
- Waiter! - The owner!
恭喜! 这些人喝什么？
Congratulations! What do these people drink?
他们想喝什么都有
Whatever they want.
太好了，给每个人都来一杯！
Great, get a drink for everyone!
格齐姆，走开！
Gezim, go away!
快点，继续！
Come on, continue!
加油，迪塞尔，左手! 让我看看你的左手! 左手！
Come on, Diesel, left! Show me your left! Left!
快点快点！
Come on, come on!
裁缝米兰? 我是丹尼洛 · 托马斯维奇
Milan the Tailor? I am Danilo Tomasovich.
我知道，有人告诉我你在找我
I know. They told me you were looking for me.
左手，迪塞尔! 加油，双手！
Left hand, Diesel! Come on, both hands!
看在上帝的份上，德拉吉尼亚是用双手把你带到了这个世界的！
Draginya brought you into the world with both hands, for God's sake!
随你怎么说，我很忙
Say what you want, I'm busy.
我是来提议商业合作的
I came to suggest a business cooperation.
我看起来像是需要老板的人吗？
Do I look like someone who needs a boss?
快，快，快! 打他的头！
Go, go, go! Come on! In the head!
打他的头! 打他！
Hit him in the head! Hit him!
你看起来像是一个不知所措的人
You look like someone who doesn't know which way to turn.
你拖拖拉拉像个二流小偷
You're dragging around like a second-rate thief,
你可以做一些正经生意
and you could do some serious business.
丹尼洛
Danilo.
你知道，我曾经有过一个老板
I've had a boss once before, you know.
我发誓再也不会有人做我的老板了
And I vowed that no one would ever be my boss ever again.
我听说他是个十足的混蛋
I heard he's a real prick.
- 而且是个傻逼 - 是的
- And a cunt. - Yes.
你看起来也是像个混蛋的傻逼
And you also look like as a prick and a cunt.
嘿，迪塞尔！
Hey, Diesel!
- 你是迪塞尔? - 赞内
- You're Diesel? - Tzane.
干得好，孩子！
Well done, boy!
在拳击比赛中，最重要的动脑，而不动手
In boxing, the most important thing is to use your head, not hands.
集中注意力，来啊，打我！
Pay attention. Come on, hit me!
- 加油! - 加油，斯马！
- Come on! - Come on, Sima!
开始！
Go!
加油，斯马! 加油！
Go, Sima! Go!
打中了他的肝脏，让他站不起来
You hit the liver and he can't get up.
没事吧，孩子！
Come on, boy!
什么肝? ！
What liver?!
他的肝脏被白兰地酒烧焦了！
His liver is burned by brandy!
丹尼洛，跟我来！
Danilo, come on, follow me!
- 日尔诺夫调查进展如何? - 是的
- So... Zhrnov? - Yes.
一切都是从那里开始的
It all started from there.
法官和维多杰都是
The judge and Vidoje were members
拆除日尔诺夫的委员会成员
of the board for the demolition of Zhrnov.
委员会有多少成员？
How many members are on that board?
九个
Nine.
有很多潜在的受害者
A good number of potential victims.
这要看情况
It depends.
如果这些都是宗教仪式上的谋杀，那么一共有9个
If these are ritual murders, then there are nine of them.
但如果是为了钱
But if this is about money,
受害者的人数要少得多
the number of victims is much smaller.
什么钱？
What money?
我有可靠消息说法官和维多杰
I have reliable information that Vidoje, the judge
还有奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇聚在米里奇家见面
and Obrad Savkovich met at Mirich's place.
商讨进行一项大额投资
To agree on a large investment.
你从哪里得到这些信息的？
Where did you get that information?
我有我的消息来源
I have my sources.
新时代报的老板，奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇？
Obrad Savkovich, the owner of the New Age?
是的
Yes.
最近，维多杰和法官赚了一大笔钱
And Vidoje and the judge were raking in cash, lately.
这需要调查一下
That needs to be checked.
就算是为了钱，但是..
Let's say this is about the money, but...
还有另外一件事把他们联系在一起，对吧？
There's another thing that connects them, right?
赌博
Gambling.
在你的俱乐部
At your club.
那不是我的俱乐部
That's not my club.
哦，是的，你只是在保护它
Oh, yeah, you're just securing it.
是的，我正在调查，你有什么问题吗？
Yes, I'm securing it, do you have a problem with that?
没有，但这对调查很重要
No, but it's important for the investigation.
我们需要地址
We need the address.
不能告诉你
Can't tell you that.
如果有什么需要调查的话，我会去做的
If something has to be checked, I'll do it.
- 你说过你会帮我们的 - 好了好了
- You said you'll help us. - Okay, okay.
现在赌博已经不那么重要了
Gambling isn't that important now.
塔尼，你能和玛雅 · 达维多维奇联系一下吗
Tane, can you check with Maya Davidovich
调查他们资金周转的银行名字
the name of the bank they operated through...
- 这样我们就能把他们联系起来? - 我试试，就这些？
- So we could connect them? - I'll try. Is that all?
目前就这些
For now.
再见！
See you!
不要那样和塔尼说话
Don't talk like that with Tane.
我来跟他沟通
Leave him to me.
这是海洛因，我们的新工作
This is heroin. Our new job.
让我们向城里的先生们介绍一种新的娱乐方式
Let's introduce the gentlemen of the metropolis to a new joy,
因为他们已经厌倦了马其顿和土耳其的鸦片
because they're already bored with Macedonian and Turkish opium.
现在他们要把这个放进他们的鼻子和血管里？
And now they're going to put this in their nose and veins, huh?
然后他们会越用越多
And they'll ask for more.
你为什么需要我？
Why do you need me?
你有很多人手，我需要他们在街上...
You have a lot of people and I need them for the street...
至于我们普通的刽子手..
And for our common executioner...
如果我没理解错的话，你还挑起了和他的战争
You also started a war with him, if I understood correctly.
我想我们共同的刽子手是，阿里姆皮耶 · 米里奇
Our common executioner is, I suppose, Alimpiye Mirich
还有整个贝尔格莱德警方
and the entire Belgrade police.
我的人民要发动战争，你打算怎么办？
My people to make war and what are you going to do?
我向你保证，贝尔格莱德警方不会很团结
I'll assure you that the Belgrade police don't have to be so united.
那个基佬佩塔尔并不是塞尔维亚唯一的势力
And that Petar the Tulip isn't the only power in Serbia.
首先，一个小礼物
A little gift, for start.
叫你的人明天来找我
Your guys will come to me tomorrow,
装上货物，在城市里转转
load the goods, go around the city,
告诉他们不要用，因为...
and tell them not to use it because...
如果这东西用多了，他们很快就会死去
If they overdose on this, they will be dead very soon.
别担心他们
Don't worry about them.
他们眼里只有白兰地...
They wouldn't trade brandy for anything...
干杯！
Cheers!
Salute!
米拉丁卡！
Miladinka!
你知道普罗米修斯是谁吗？
Do you know who Prometheus was?
不知道
No, Alimpiye.
他给人们生火
He gave people fire.
众神惩罚了他
And the gods punished him for it.
你打算什么时候惩罚我？
When are you going to punish me?
奇妙的幻觉世界
MAGIC LILLY WONDERFUL WORLD OF ILLUSION
怎么回事？
What's going on?
怎么回事? ！
What's going on?!
- 你知道我是谁吗? - 我知道
- Do you know who I am? - I do.
将军先生，你没必要这么夸张
Mr. General, you didn't have to be so theatrical.
你真以为你可以耍我吗？
Do you really think you can fuck with me, huh?
如果这是一个玩笑，那就有点过火了
If this is a joke, then it's very brutal.
但如果不是，那么这就是一个巨大的错误
But if it's not, then this is a huge mistake.
你为什么把那些照片给萨夫科维奇？
Why did you give those photos to Savkovich?
给奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇？
To Obrad Savkovich?
你还认识别的萨夫科维奇？
You know some other Savkovich?
什么照片？
What photos?
你以为你可以这样蒙混过关吗? ！
Do you think you can get rid of me like that?!
将军先生，不是我干的
Mr. General, I didn't do it.
我发誓我没有
I swear I didn't.
根本没有理由
Tell me, why?
我为什么要破坏我们长期卓有成效的合作呢？
Why would I ruin our long-standing fruitful cooperation?
好好想想！
Think!
我能从中得到什么呢？
What would I gain from that?
讨萨夫科维奇的欢心？
Savkovich's affection?
讨他的纳粹老板们欢心？
The affection of his Nazi bosses?
他能给我什么
What can he give me
你不能我的东西？
that you haven't already given me?
我发誓不是我干的
I swear I didn't do it.
接下来这样
Here's how we'll do it.
我再给你一次机会
I'll give you another chance.
但只有一次机会
But only one.
萨夫科维奇必须消失
Savkovich must disappear.
永远消失
Forever.
否则，我让你和普里萨德
Otherwise, there won't be even ashes...
灰飞烟灭
left from Prizad and you.
我说的够清楚了吗？
Do I make myself clear?
一清二楚
As clear as a day.
你没多少时间了
You don't have much time.
尼什基! 这怎么回事？
Nishky! What the fuck is this?
你的人砸了我的店，驱散了我的客人，快把他带走！
Your guy broke my bar, dispersed my guests, get him out of here!
哦，我的老厚米！
Oh, for God's sake!
天呐，我对你做了什么！
Dear Lord, what have I done to you?!
你说呢！
You name it!
你很幸运没有上帝，否则你就完蛋了
You're lucky there's no God, otherwise you'd be fucked.
我们可以在任何时候讨论这个话题
We can talk about this topic whenever you want.
停！
Silence!
你长高了
You've grown a bit.
去你妈的！
Fuck you!
看看他！
Look at him!
坐下！
Sit!
接着弹！
Play!
告诉我...
Tell me...
你又来讨论什么狗屁共产主义了？
Did you come to talk shit about communism again?
我们待会聊那个
Don't worry, we'll get to that.
我听说你明天早上要去马其顿
I've heard you're going to Macedonia tomorrow morning.
哇，你真厉害！
Wow, you're good!
你从沃亚和阿皮斯那里学到了一切？
You learned everything from Voya and Apis, huh?
- 为了我们死去的兄弟 - 是的
- For our departed brothers. - Yes.
愿他们的灵魂安息！
God rest their soul!
我真的很抱歉
Oh, I'm really sorry about that.
你还在为马其顿的鸦片走私贩工作？
So, you still work for Macedonian opium smugglers?
是的，但好像又不完全是
I do, but it's almost like I don't.
他们给我的还不够
What they send me is not enough,
因为我四面受敌
because I am pressed from every side.
他们压力也很大，不是吗？
They are pressed too, aren't they?
是的
They are.
你听说那个疯子阿尔索夫回来找他们了吗？
Did you hear that crazy Hadzi Arsov came back to them?
是的，我自己都不敢相信
Yes, I couldn't believe myself.
无论他出现在哪里，他都会把一切都搞砸
Wherever he appears, he fucks everything up.
你要把那个疯子带到这里来
You'll bring me that lunatic here.
- 你他妈的为什么需要他? - 这不重要
- Why the fuck you need him? - Doesn't matter.
告诉他莱斯科瓦茨的老板德约科
Just tell him that Master Djoko from Leskovac
正在紧急寻找他
is urgently looking for him.
- 德约科? ! - 他知道那是谁
- Djoko?! - He will know who that is.
天啊! 你们这些共产党真是疯了！
Jesus! You communists are crazy!
其他的名字都有人用了
Well, all the other names were taken.
我希望你从海边给我带来了好消息
I hope you brought me good news from the coast.
没有比这更好的了
You couldn't have hoped for better.
我们会帮你安排运输
We'll help you with the transport.
我每周至少需要一次
I'll need it at least once a week.
好的
Okay.
我会帮你联系我们在斯普利特的朋友
I'll connect you with our friend from Split
那边当然也不会有什么问题
and there will certainly be no problems.
你可以立即开始组织
You can start organizing immediately.
祝你好运
Good luck.
我们不要把运气和生意混为一谈
Let's not mix luck and business.
我们遵守了所有的协议我很满意
We have complied with all the agreements and I'm satisfied,
但米里奇先生不会高兴得知我们的小小合作
but Mr. Mirich won't be happy to hear about our small cooperation.
那是你的问题
That's your problem.
我要发动一场战争
I'll start a war.
这就是我们所希望的
That's what we hope for.
非常好
Very nice.
探长！
Inspector!
我发现了一些有趣的东西
I've found something interesting.
什么？
What?
这份名单实际上是一份来自亚塔汗贫民窟的名单
The list of names is actually a list of people from Yataghan slum
表示他们自愿搬出去
who signed up to voluntarily move out
让他们在那里建造一座新城市
to build a new city in that place.
你确定吗？
Are you sure about that?
是的，一切都写在法官的文件里
Yes, everything is written in the judge's papers.
他们愿意为了一些可怜的补偿而搬出去
They move out for some miserable compensation.
只需要把这个清单加到抗议书上
It was only needed to add this list to the remonstrance
亚塔汗贫民窟的命运就此注定
and the fate of the Yataghan slum would be sealed.
我不相信他们会自愿这么做
I don't believe they would do it voluntarily.
有人欺骗了他们
Someone tricked them.
也许凶手就来自亚塔汗贫民窟
Maybe the killer is someone from Yataghan slum.
凶手是这个圈子里的人
The killer is someone from this business.
或者是曾经在圈子里工作的人
Or someone who used to be in this business.
这关系到一大笔钱
Big money is at stake.
所以，原因就是亚塔汗贫民窟
So, the reason is Yataghan slum.
把钥匙给我
Give me the keys.
你不去警局吗？
You're not going to Glavnjacha?
不
No.
我接到一个电话，可以为我们解决很多问题
I received a call which could solve a lot of things for us.
谁的电话？
From who?
奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇
From Obrad Savkovich.
萨夫科维奇? 新时代报？
Savkovich? The New Age?
是的
That one.
回头见！
See you later!
你只需要让他放松，让他信任你
You just have to relax him, make him trust you.
他可能会很小心，他第一次不会单独来的
He'll probably be careful, he won't come alone the first time.
之后呢？
And after that?
我们会邀请他去一个中立的地方，那里有很多人
We'll invite him to a neutral place where there are a lot of people.
在一个不会引起怀疑的地方
In a place that doesn't cause doubt.
之后呢？
And after that?
好吧，怎么了？
Okay, what's wrong?
我不喜欢这样
I don't like that.
没什么喜不喜欢的
There's nothing to like or not.
你按我说的做...
You do what you're told and...
亲爱的教授，革命不是请求，而是下达命令
Dear professor, the revolution doesn't ask - it gives orders.
我以为革命是另外一回事
I thought the revolution was something else.
是启蒙，是对年轻人的教育
That it's the enlightenment, the education of young people,
而不是盲目执行党的命令！
and not the blind execution of party orders!
你错了
Well, you're wrong.
别跟我说那些废话
And don't give me those speeches.
你在瑞士不是这么说的
You spoke differently in Switzerland.
我就是这么说的，但你没有仔细听，而且..
I didn't speak differently, but you're a bad listener and...
我听得很仔细
I listened to you very well
所以我才在那里做了那些事！
and that's why I did what I did there!
好了，到此为止
Okay, that's enough for now.
不，这就是我和你在一起的原因！
No, that's why I'm here with you!
我说够了! 仔细听我说！
I said it's enough! Listen to me carefully!
听我说! 小心点！
Listen to me! Carefully!
我们不能假装你很天真
We can't both pretend you were just naive,
但是当你一个人在国外，等着你丈夫
but you were just bored while you were alone abroad
操遍日内瓦的每个人的时候很无聊
waiting for your husband to fuck everyone in Geneva!
好像你不知道
As if you didn't know
你带到我房间的土耳其人会怎么收场? ！
how that Turkish shit you brought to my room would end?!
你很清楚我是谁，我在做什么
You knew very well who I was and what I was doing.
所以现在不要装傻了
So don't pretend to be silly now.
明白了吗？
Is that clear?
是的
Yes.
等等
Wait.
哦，我的教授..
Oh, my professor...
这不是学生练习
These are not student exercises.
战场上不许说话
There's no talking on the field.
只和革命的敌人作斗争
Only fight against the enemies of the revolution.
当你打架的时候，手一定会脏的
When you fight, you have to get dirty.
不要...
Just don't...
别让我失望
Don't let me down.
亲爱的玛雅，你能让我的合同快点签完吗？
Dear Maya, will you make me happy with the finished contract?
什么合同？
What contract?
购买铅矿的合同！
For the purchase of the lead mine, for God's sake!
我们已经等了好几天了，时间不多了！
We've been waiting for days, we're running out of time!
- “我们”是谁，拉贾奇基先生? - 投资人啊！
- Who is "we", Mr. Rajachki? - Investors!
我们不是唯一对这笔交易感兴趣的公司
We're not the only ones interested in that purchase.
拉贾奇基先生，玛雅把文件工作托付给了我
Mr. Rajachki, Maya entrusted the job to me.
恐怕我还没有检查完所有资料
I'm afraid I haven't been able to check everything up,
你可以告诉你的投资人，耐心点
so you can tell your investors to arm themselves with patience.
- 你听到他说的了 - 是的
- You heard him. - Yes.
但我不能说我喜欢这个答案
But I can't say I like the answer.
那你为什么急着叫我来？
And then why did you call me to come urgently?
我有事问你
I'll ask you directly.
你有没有在我不知情的情况下
Did you have any contact
和维也纳的总部联系？
with our headquarters in Vienna, without my knowledge?
或者更准确地说
Or, more precisely,
诺维奇伯爵来贝尔格莱德的时候
did you have any contact with Count Nowicki
你们有联系吗
while he was in Belgrade?
就算我联系了，跟你有什么关系？
Even if I did, why does it concern you?
我是组织的老大！
I'm your Order Master!
当然，那又怎样？
Of course. So what?
- 这太过分了! - 过分？
- Well, this is outrageous! - Outrageous?
你才把我们的组织搞得太过分了
Outrageous is what you made of our organization.
你扼杀了它
You killed it.
你让别人随意践踏我们的组织
You let others overtake her.
如果你认为组织应该在哪里不会被注意到
And if you thought that it would not be noticed
那你就错了！
where it should be, you were wrong!
你怎么能这样跟我说话? ！
Where did you get the idea that you could talk to me like that?!
海涅曼夫人
Mrs. Heinemann,
当你的祖先还在马赫瓦买卖猪肉的时候
while your ancestors traded pigs in Machva,
我的祖先已经在施蒂里亚建了城堡
mine built castles in Styria.
我这么跟你说话是因为我的出身允许我这么做
I am addressing you as my origin allows me to.
你最好趁还有时间考虑一下你的行为
You'd better think about your actions while you still have time.
如果我是你...
If I were you...
我会尽快签署那份合同！
I would sign that contract as soon as possible!
他说的有一定道理
He's partly right.
事态超越了我们的能力...
Events surpass us, bypass...
- 你必须离开这里 - 不！
- You have to get out of here. - No!
还不行！
Not yet!
邮局
POST OFFICE
下午好
Good afternoon.
尽快给维也纳发一份电报
A telegram to Vienna, as soon as possible.
“这笔交易没有达成”
"The deal is not made."
“我认为，在这种情况下，这是不可能的”
"I don't think it will be possible in these conditions."
“事情变得越来越复杂，但我会解释一切”
"Things are getting complicated, but I will clarify everything."
“我会尽快回信”
"I'll get back to you soon."
二十七个字，你忘了签名
Twenty-seven words. You forgot the signature.
不用签名
I didn't.
他们会知道发信人是谁
They'll know who the sender is.
新时代印刷厂
NEW AGE PRINTING HOUSE
下午好
Good afternoon.
斯坦科 · 普莱蒂科西奇，重案组
Stanko Pletikosich, crime and sexual offences.
- 欢迎 - 谢谢
- Welcome. - Thanks.
- 探长先生! - 拉雷！
- Mr. Inspector! - Lale!
- 你在这儿干什么? - 工作
- What are you doing here? - Working.
你终于找到了一份体面的工作
You finally found a decent job,
这样我就不用再逮捕你了
so I don't have to arrest you anymore.
你以前也不用逮捕我
Well, you didn't have to do it before, either.
我别无选择，你偷东西偷得太疯狂了
I had to, Lale. You stole like crazy.
你还在打拳吗？
Are you still boxing?
是的，但是是跟字母打，我应该把这个放在哪里，老板？
Yes, but with letters. Where should I put this, boss?
放在角落
Put it in the corner, Bozadzija.
你是...
And you are...
- 斯坦科 · 普莱蒂科西奇 - 普莱蒂科西奇督察！
- Stanko Pletikosich. - Inspector Pletikosich!
我是韦塞利诺维奇，印刷厂的负责人
Veselinovich, head of the printing house.
- 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
- Nice to meet you. - You too.
欢迎来到新时代
Welcome to the New Age.
跟我来，萨夫科维奇先生在等你，这边走
Follow me, Mr. Savkovich is waiting for you. This way.
新时代报
NEW AGE
探长先生！
Mr. Inspector!
你能来我很高兴，失陪一下
Thanks for coming. Excuse me for a second.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
有什么可以帮你的吗？
How may I help you?
如果我没记错的话
If I'm not mistaken,
你在调查那些可怕的谋杀案
you're working on cases of these horrific murders.
- 萨夫科维奇先生! - 不好意思
- Mr. Savkovich! - Excuse me.
是的，你了解案情吗？
Yes, I am. Do you know something about them?
不，但我认识受害者
No, but I knew the victims.
我们在日尔诺夫纪念碑的委员会共事
We were together in the Committee
的委员会共事
for the construction of the monument on Zhrnov.
你认为你会因此而处于危险之中吗？
Do you think you are in danger because of that?
我还以为你会告诉我呢
I thought maybe you would tell me that.
到目前为止，我们还没有发现被害人和日尔诺夫之间的联系
So far, we haven't found a connection
但调查仍在进行中
between the dead and Zhrnov, but the investigation is ongoing.
如果我向你透露一些事实，我能指望你保密吗？
If I confide some facts to you, can I count on your discretion?
你知道我不能保证
You know I can't promise that.
好吧，我愿意冒这个险
Fair enough. Okay, I'll risk it.
普莱蒂科西奇先生，我没有成家
Mr. Pletikosich, I don't have a family.
我把我的一生都投入到这家公司，投入到新时代
I have invested my whole life in this company, in the New Age.
我深信我的使命，我并不为此感到抱歉
I deeply believe in my mission and I'm not sorry for that.
但这是一份压力很大的工作
But it's a stressful job.
这让我很紧张
It costs me a lot of nerves.
所以偶尔我会让自己放松一下
So occasionally I allow myself some relaxation.
可以说，这并不完全合法
Which is not exactly legal, so to speak.
你是指地下赌场？
You mean poker?
你知道？
You know about that?
那你一定也知道你的前任上司
Then you must know that your former chief
是赌局的组织者之一
was the organizer of poker games.
而且他和死者有业务往来
And that he had business relations with the deceased.
你也和他有业务往来吗？
Have you had business relations with him?
是的
Yes.
米里奇先生邀请我参与
Mr. Mirich invited me to participate in the construction
贫民窟改建工程项目
of a new settlement at Yataghan slum.
但我不确定在这些事情发生之后
But I'm not sure that after all this,
我和我的合伙人会继续做生意
my partners and I will stay in the business.
法官和维多杰也参与其中了吗吗？
Did the judge and Vidoje have any interest in that?
我不知道，也不在乎
I don't know and I don't care.
我只知道法官应该给我许可证
All I know is that the judge should have provided the permits,
还有迪米特里耶维奇在收集签名
and that Dimitriyevich was collecting some signatures.
签名？
Signatures?
什么签名？
What signatures?
亚塔汗贫民窟
To build this new settlement
改建项目的签名
on the land of Yataghan slum.
但是最近，他们的工作做得并不好
But lately, they haven't been doing well.
气氛有点紧张
There was some tension,
说了一些难听的话... 威胁
some hard words... threats.
严重的威胁
Serious threats.
如果你明白我的意思
If you know what I mean.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
是吗？
Really?
你的朋友不满意你送的东西吗？
Your friends are not happy with the delivery?
- 是的 - 那又怎样？
- They are. - So?
一个叫托马斯维奇的人出现了
Some Tomasovich appeared.
黑山人，他和马其顿人合作
Montenegrin. He works with Macedonians.
我朋友说他的货更好
They say he's doing very well.
我们得到消息说他正在打造一个新的运输系统
We have information that he's launching a new transport.
从亚得里亚海到美洲
From the Adriatic to America.
- 怎么会? - 你说呢
- How come? - You tell me.
是的，他还和贫民窟的人有联系
Yes, he also connected with those from Yataghan slum.
- 贫民窟的什么人? - 猪
- Who are they? - Pigs.
他们控制着贝尔格莱德的一部分生意
They control one part of the business in Belgrade.
在你眼皮底下？
Even though you're here?
不，他们是...
No, they are...
一个小问题
A minor problem.
如果只是个小问题，这位先生是不会开口的
If they were a minor problem, this gentleman wouldn't mention it.
这位先生只是不知道什么时候该闭嘴，仅此而已
This gentleman just doesn't know when to shut up, that's all.
- 米里奇! - 什么事？
- Mirich! - Yes?
如果托马斯维奇从斯普利特港口运输
If Tomasovich starts the transport from Split,
那么背后一定有个很有权势的人
then someone very powerful is behind it.
我以为一切都在你的掌控之中
I thought it's under your control.
没有后台保护，这样的事情是不可能发生的
Such work isn't done without someone's protection.
戈迪纳先生
Mr. Godina...
我向你保证，我和这个国家最高层的关系
I assure you that my connections to the top of the country
比以往任何时候都要强大
are stronger than ever.
所以你完全不用担心
So you can be completely at ease.
我真诚地希望如此
I sincerely hope so.
祝你今天过得愉快
Have a nice day.
维利加！
Veriga!
我要你为我做两件事
I want you to do two things for me.
首先...
First...
在我让你说之前不要说话
Never talk until I let you.
- 清楚了吗? - 是的,老大
- Is that clear? - Yes, boss.
第二...
And second...
组织人手
Gather the people.
我们是要发动战争吗？
Are we starting a war?
在某种程度上
In some way.
这更像是一盘棋
This will look more like a game of chess.
注意你的一举一动
Take care of your every move.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
你怀疑我吗？
Do you doubt me?
我怀疑每个人
Everyone.
我们去贫民窟
We'll hit the Yataghan slum.
晚上好
Good evening.
这是什么意思
I don't understand.
La Roche公司的朋友们
My friends from La Roche
只是想表达我们的诚意
just wanted to convince you that we are serious.
这只是一小步
It's a small advance.
我们知道你做生意很谨慎
We know you're a careful person when it comes to business.
预付款... 我很感激
An advance... I appreciate that.
然后呢? 你想从我这里得到什么？
And now what? What do you want from me?
那你就要和我的朋友谈了，我只是个信使
You have to discuss it with them, I'm just a courier.
信使...
Just a courier...
如果他们的出价和信使一样有吸引力
Well, if their offers are as attractive as the couriers,
我们会合作的
we'll work it out.
好吧
Okay.
明天见
See you tomorrow then.
- 再见 - 再见
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
所以迪米特里耶维奇在收集反对拆迁的签名
So Dimitriyevich was collecting signatures against the demolition.
事实上，这些签名就是
And in fact, those signatures were an agreement
拆除贫民窟的同意书
to demolish the Yataghan slum.
他们就是这样欺骗穷人的
That's how they tricked the poor.
这就是他们开始合法重建所需要的一切
That's all they needed to start building legally.
在这一切的背后...
And behind all that...
是阿里姆皮耶 · 米里奇
is Alimpiye Mirich.
我真不敢相信迪米特里耶维奇会同意为阿里姆皮耶 · 米里奇工作
I can't believe Dimitriyevich agreed to work for Alimpiye Mirich.
那萨夫科维奇呢？
And Savkovich?
他是什么角色？
What is he doing there?
奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇是个商人
Well, Obrad Savkovich is a businessman,
他看到了一个很好的机会
he saw a good opportunity in that.
当他感觉事情朝着奇怪的方向发展时
When he saw that things were going in a strange direction,
他会告诉我
then he called me.
修道士，法官，维多杰...
The Monk, the judge, Vidoje...
他们都是由一个人联系在一起的
They are all connected by one man.
迪米特里耶维奇会给我们解释清楚
Dimitriyevich will have to explain some things to us.
借个火？
Have some fire?
你是什么人? ！
Who are you?!
我是你这辈子见到的最后一个人
I'm the last one you'll see in life.
嘿！
Hey!
去吧，孩子们！
Let's go, boys!
你又开始喝酒了？
You're drinking again?
好像很重要似的
Like it matters...
不，这是值得表扬的
No, it's commendable.
我一直不信任不喝酒的男人
I've always been suspicious of men who don't drink.
别扯淡了
Don't bullshit.
塔尼，我知道你非常爱索尼娅...
Tane, I know you loved Sonya very much...
她是怎么死的？
How did she die?
钝器，瞬间致死...
A blunt object, instant death...
如果这能让你好受一点的话
If that means anything to you.
在我看来，她出现在那里纯属偶然
It seems to me that she was there by accident.
太迟了
She was late.
她没能逃出来
She didn't make it out of there.
- 什么东西着火了? - 我着火了！
- What the fuck is burning? - I am on fire!
不要停，是我着火了
Please don't stop! I'm on fire.
- 快... - 等等！
- Come... - Wait!
等等！
Wait!
发生了什么？
What happened?
那维多杰呢? 他的舌头被割掉了？
What about Vidoje? His tongue was cut off?
我认为凶手在传递一些信息
I think the killer is sending some messages.
他切掉死者的食指，挖出死者的眼睛
He cuts the victims' forefinger, takes out their eyes,
割掉死者的舌头，还把老鼠留在犯罪现场..
cuts their tongues, leaves rats at the crime scene...
你是说，凶手是在惩罚他们？
You mean, like, punishing them?
是的
Yes.
惩罚什么样的人才会割掉舌头呢？
And who is punished by cutting off the tongue?
- 撒谎的那种 - 没错
- The one who lies. - That's right.
而且维多杰是个众所周知的骗子
And Vidoje is a well-known liar.
他撒了无数次谎
He lied countless times,
更别提他多少次作伪证
not to mention how many times he testified falsely.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
孩子，你死定了
Well, kid, you're fucked now.
你为什么两手空空地对着枪? ！
Why are you running empty-handed to the gun?!
你跟你爹一个德行! 回家去！
You're just like your father! Go home!
回家去！
Go home!
- 你没事吧? - 我们没事，但他有事
- Are you okay? - We are, but he isn't.
兄弟，我们认识
Dude, we know each other.
维多杰与塞萨洛尼基进程有关吗？
Do you know if Vidoje had anything to do with the Thessaloniki process?
我想有关
I think he had.
怎么突然提起这个？
How did you remember that now?
这一切都围绕着黑手党
Everything revolves around the Black Hand.
好像一切都是相互关联的
It's like everything is connected.
关联？
Connected?
乍一看
At first glance,
好像没关系
it seems it isn't,
但也许这就是关键
but maybe that's the solution.
够了，孩子们，我们走！
That's enough, boys! Let's go!
快点！
Come on!
我一点也不喜欢这样
I don't like this at all.
太棒了，真的太棒了
It's wicked. Really wicked.
小心点，塔尼
Be careful, Tane.